We, Super Turn! Strong Energy! Positive! Exciting! Soul! From! Nagoya!
Team Sharts! with purple, purple, kakkari, and daikoku yujiki of the
Muraho series of Ukka.
Please give us your best regards.
I'm sure those of you who know what I'm talking about may have figured it out,
This is recorded after the dialogue.
I have already talked a lot,
Yes, that's right. We talked a lot.
I am still warming up,
Tokyo YakanLand, for the event to be held in September,
I would like to play a game to strengthen the bond between us,
I would like to play some games.
The first game is the Meow Meow Game.
The Meow Meow Game.
Have you heard of it?
It's your first time.
It's my first time too.
Let me explain the rules,
The player who plays the cat turns over a card from the deck of theme cards,
The player who plays the cat turns over one card from the deck of theme cards and reads the theme of the next card that comes up.
There are many subjects written on the card, and I read them out.
Then, the cat player looks at the theme card and says the word that comes to his/her mind in cat language.
For example, "Meow meow meow,
For example, meow meow meow.
Meow meow meow meow.
Apple.
Correct!
We will tell you in cat language like so.
And the player on the answer side listens to that cat language,
and guess the correct answer, just like now.
There is no penalty if the answer is wrong,
We would like to keep on giving out positive answers.
If you guess the correct answer, you get one of these cat frames.
It's cute. A little cat.
Or if the player playing the cat can't think of any words,
If the player playing the cat can't think of a word, or if the player answering the question doesn't know the answer at all, he or she can pass,
I'd like to answer more and more correctly.
The goal is to reach 20 cat frames in 5 minutes.
This time, with a special rule, we will switch the cat role at the 2 minutes and 30 seconds mark,
We will switch the cat role at the 2 minutes and 30 seconds mark, and the two of us will have a total of 5 minutes to complete all of them.
We would like to get started right away,
Which one do you want to do?
Which do you want to do?
Either one is fine.
We'll play rock-paper-scissors-scissors and start with the cat.
OK.
Okay, let's go. Ready.
First, "goo", then "jankenpoi".
Then, I'll play the cat.
Mizuki will be the cat and I will be the one who answers.
I'll be the one to answer.
I have been prepared.
I'm wearing a catsuit because I have a cat,
I will switch from catsuit to catsuit.
Yes.
Pink.
It's so cute.
I haven't worn it for a long time.
It doesn't happen often.
It doesn't happen often. I don't know,I don't think so. I don't know,
What kind of pictures did you put on it? It's like...
It's cute.
It's cute. It looks great on you.
I'm embarrassed.
It's cute.
Well, I'll do my best to play the cat.
I'll do my best to answer.
Okay, let the nyah-nyah game begin!
Start!
Ta-da!
Mammal name.
Mammal who?
Nyanya nyanya nyanya nyanya nyanya nyanya nyanya nyanya.
Nyan-nyan-nyan-nyan-nyan.
Hamster? No, not a hamster.
Not a mammal?
Who's a mammal?
Who?
What's a mammal?
Meow, meow, meow, meow.
Mammals are the ones that eat?
No, they don't.
How do they eat?
It's cute.
Cute. Okay, I said something else.
Did you just do that? No?
Can I spass live sound or something?
No, it's fine.
Vegetable name.
Nyan-nyan-nyan.
Tomato?
No, no.
Nyan nyan nyan.
It's a vegetable, right? Because it's a vegetable.
Three letters. Not tomato.
Nyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyanny.
Nyanya-nyanya.
Carrot?
Nyanya nyanya.
Nya nya nya nya.
Nyannyannyannyannyannyanny.
Nyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyanny.
Lettuce.
Cabbage? Correct!
One!
Still one.
Here we go.
The title of a romantic movie.
I don't know.
What's a romance movie?
Nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan.
Nyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyanny.
Is it 4 letters?
It's very difficult.
Nyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyanny.
A love movie.
Very famous.
I don't mind if you pass.
I don't know. Please pass.I'm a little unsure. Please pass.
OK, let's go.
Things start from the tower.
Nyonya nyonya.
And the clock.
No, it's not.
Nyanya.
Nyanya. Tower.
Tomato.
Correct!
Cat cat.
Things used for cleaning.
Nyah-nyah-nyah.
Vacuum cleaner.
Correct!
Steady!
Dong.
Still 3 pieces.
Cartoon title.
Nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan.
Oni-no-Blade.
Nyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyanny.
Is it an anime?
Yes, it is.
Nyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyanny.
Crayon Shin-chan.
Too bad.
Isn't it close?
Isn't it regrettable? It's not Doraemon.
Sounds great.
Nyanya nyanya nyanya.
Nyanya nyanya nyanya nyanya.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Oh, that's not right!
Funny?
It's not right.
Okay, okay, okay.
Yes, yes, yes.
Numbers? Numbers?
Nyan!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
One!
Meow!
Three!
6!
kyan!
Meow! 7!
That's not a kitten.
Not a kitten.
10!
Nyan!
2!
Ha ha ha ha!
kyan!
3!
kyan!Meow!
Meow! Meow!
Uh, 5!
Meow!
5!
10!
Ha ha ha ha!
kyan!
Nyan!
Oh, this hand has nothing to do with it, right?
Oh, this is Nyan!
Isn't that 3?
Nyan!
Eight!
Nine!
Nyan!
Isn't it 20?
10! 10!
Meow!
Nine!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Meow!
Am I getting too hung up on 1s and 10s?
What is it, 1 or 0?
Zero!
There's one missing!
What?
Nyan!
Six!
What? What?
Meow!
Three!
Two!
What?
Meow!
Is it one digit already?
Yeah.
You mean there's no one in the single digits?
Meow!
Eight!
Seven!
7!
Six!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
5!
Meow!
4!
Correct!
Oh, four!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Oh, switching?
What? Switch?
Did you just say "four" on one?
Four!4!
I got it! I got it!
Excuse me, sir!
I'll just guess this much!
Okay, I'll play the cat next.
I'll take this one, White, that you prepared.
Yes!
I'll show you!
This is not my first time.
It is the first time, but a little bit.
Like this.
Yes!
I'd like to go!
Wow! Okay, then!
Let's go!
Let's get ready!
Oh...
Something you see a lot in the summer?
Nyan-nyan-nyan!
Fireworks!
That's right!
Oh, I haven't moved it a bit, so...
Well...
I'm not so good at cooking...
Nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan!
Fried egg!
You're right!
Oh!
Good!
Just one more question...
Let's see...
Field day competition!
Nyan-nyan-nyan!
Run!
Mileage!
Running!
Nyannyannyan!
Nyan-nyan-nyan!
It's a sprint! It's a sprint!
Relay!
Running!
Isn't there another way to say "kakko-kko"?
Nyan-nyan-nyan!
Time!
Wah!
Tokimoto!
That's right!
To! And! And!
Uh, let's see...
One Piece character
Meow! Meow!
Nyanya, Chopper!
That's right!
It's Chopper.
The name of a herbivore.
Herbivore?
Herbivore...
What, a herbivore!What, oh, you're a herbivore!
Yes, yes, yes.
It's grass, uh...
Meow.
Cat.
Who eats grass?
mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia
Elephant... I made a mistake. I think I got everything right.
I'm talking about nya nya nya? yes
Snake... uh, no...
Herbivore? Herbivore? Is he famous? Very famous.
Rabbit? Uh, no. Meow.
Squirrel. - Oh, no, I got it wrong. - Big?
It's like, uh, the Nakagura ranch or something. Ranch? Etta?
Uh, no.
Birds? They eat a lot of different things. Birds?
Horses? Cows? That kind? That way? That way? That way?
Pony? Pony? That way? That way.
That way? Meow? Meow!
What? Is it famous? Yes, it's famous.
I'd love to win this one.
What? Cows and horses? That kind. Etniel?
Etniel? Oh, no. Etniel? Etniel? You don't have an Etniel?
What? Who? No, no, no.
Now I won't tell you the answer. You won't tell me? No, I won't tell you.
Papas, let's go, papas, let's go, papas, let's go, papas, papas.
It's a snake. - Huh?
Jan? The answer to the herbivore question...
It's a goat
Yes, it eats a lot of things... a lot of things... but it eats goats...
A goat... interesting...
I like it, it's fun, it's fun, it's fun, it's fun
I got three, I got four, seven, lucky seven!
Lucky seven.
What's a mammal? Mammal is a lion.
Is a lion a mammal?
Is there a difference between a predator and a mammal?
You know, you're born as a baby and you grow up with boobs and...
So that's how you divide them.
Is that what you mean?
And dogs?
And humans?
Yes, there are humans, too.
But not frogs?
Frogs are born from eggs.
What is born from an egg?
Beehives.
So do daisies.
So birds are also beehives?
Birds are cooked.
Birds are called birds.
That's a good study.
I learned a lot.
It was a good game to learn.
Please try it, everyone.